radiobeta.com 2009-08-27

# PrivacyPolicy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains our policy regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. By accessing our Web site or using our services, you consent to our information practices. 

**What Information is Collected on this Web site?**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address. We collect no information on consumers who browse our Web page. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as radios that users add to their playlist. If you supply us with your email address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

**This Site Contains Links to Other Sites**  
RadioBeta is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which the Site links or to which link to the Site. By clicking on a link, logo or other item, please note that you may no longer be on the RadioBeta Site. To check what Internet location you are on, note the URL at the top and/or bottom of your browser. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of that website whenever interacting with any website.

**Notification of Changes**  
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our Services change and expand. If your information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Once any changes that we make to this Privacy Policy become effective, your continued use of the Site after such time will signify your acceptance of the new terms.

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, please contact priva@radiobeta.com.
